早安梦想书用户
good morning dream book users
嗯
um
我想给你一个关于如何
I want to give you a quick start on how
使用 Koya SS
to use the Koya SS
Dreamboat 回购的快速入门这样你就可以快速
Dreamboat repo so that you can quickly
开始训练你自己更多
get going with training your own more
嗯这个快速入门不会是
um this quick start is not going to be
关于如何实际安装 Korea
about how to actually install the Korea
SS 你实际上可以从 GitHub 下载它，
SS you can actually download it from
如果你搜索
GitHub if you search for
bmltis slash Koya assessed 你将
bmltis slash Koya assessed you'll be
能够找到
able to find a copy
该软件的副本然后你可以克隆
of the software and then you can clone
你可以按照说明
and you can follow the instructions on
如何需要
how like what are the required
依赖项和 安装步骤
dependencies and the installation steps
到达你
to get going up to the point where you
实际去的地方，你启动 GUI 来
actually go and you start the GUI to
实际训练你的模型，所以你使用
actually train your model so you use
这个命令 python dream boot
this command python dream boot
underscore gui.pi 这将使
underscore gui.pi and this will get the
训练器运行的 GUI 所以让我们从
GUI for the trainer running so let's
那里开始 然后我将向您展示如何
start there and then I'll show you how
使用 GUI 来训练您自己的
you can use the GUI to train your own
模型，
model
因此我们将进入 excess
so we're going to go into the excess
文件夹，您可以看到 venp 已经
folder you can see that the venp is
处于活动状态，因为
already active because it's important
您需要激活虚拟
you need to activate your virtual
环境以便它 如果
environment so that it runs properly if
你只是安装它，它会正常运行然后它会
you just install it then it's going to
默认激活但是如果你在
be activated by default but if you go
呃你实际上关闭了
back after uh you actually closed
所有它们已经准备好的
everything they are ready with the
计算机之后返回然后如果你想再次使用它
computer then if you want to use it
你将需要运行这个
again you're gonna need to run this
命令就像 这是点反斜杠
command like which is the dot backslash
是 EnV
be EnV
反斜杠脚本，然后激活
backslash scripts and then activate
，这就是你实际激活
and that's how you actually activate the
版本的方式所以让我们开始
version so let's start
python
真正启动
really boot
我不想通过馅饼得到它
I don't want to get it through the pie
，这将提高程度
and this is going to fire up the degree
，现在它是 准备好加载，所以我们
and now it is ready to load so we're
要控制点击那个链接，
gonna control click on that link and
这将为韩国党卫军教练员带来无线电用户界面，
this is going to bring the radio UI for
Korea SS trainer
所以有几个
so there's a couple of
选项卡，我们将通过
tabs we're kind of going to go through
那些对你很重要的选项卡 将
the ones that are important to you what
需要所以第一个是
you're going to need so the first one is
你需要使用一个小的权利当
you need to use a sore small right when
你想训练一些东西你需要
you want to train something you need to
向模型添加一些东西所以
add something to a model so there's a
这里有几个选项你可以使用可选的
couple of options here you can use the
快速选择在这里你可以使用
optional Quick Picks here you can use
就像将稳定扩散扩散
like either diffuse the stable diffusion
到一个底座一样，您可以使用这些演示
to one base you can use these demo
扩散 2.1，它是 768 x 768
diffusion 2.1 which is the 768 by 768
模型，您可以使用稳定扩散
model you could use stable diffusion
视图。15 或 v.14
view.15 or v.14
如果您想使用快速选择，那么
if you want to use the Quick Picks then
您只需点击让我们 看到我们
you just literally click on let's see we
想在 2.1 基础上训练，它将在
want to train on the 2.1 base it's going
to fill in the 2.1 base free train model
那里填写 2.1 基础免费训练模型名称，然后这就是它
name there and then that's how it could
开始测试的方式你也可以选择使用
start testing you could also opt to use
这个文件图标打开然后
this file icon to open up and then
这就是你要做的事情 请注意，
that's something you're going to notice
您已经看到实际的
right you've seen the actual
弹出窗口在浏览器后面打开
pop-up window open behind the browser
，这有点
and that's kind of a little bit of a
消除了，现在 GUI 弹出
eliminations right now the GUI pop-up
窗口不会在顶部打开，因此您
windows will not open on top so that you
可能不得不去钓鱼 它在
may have to go and fish for it behind
你的浏览器窗口后面，尤其是当它被
your browser window especially if it was
最大化时，你不会看到它打开，所以如果
maximized you wouldn't see it open so if
你点击按钮，它
you click on the button and it does
似乎什么也没做，那么只需最小化
appear to do nothing then just minimize
或移动你的浏览器窗口，
or move your browser window around and
然后你就会发现它在后面
then you are going to find it behind
所以 回到那里，你可以去
so going back there you could go and
选择一个模型，呃让我
pick for example a model uh let me go
去我妈妈的文件夹，你可以
and get to my mom folder and you could
去选择一个你想要的模型，
go and pick one of the models you want
例如我们要选择这个
we're going to pick for example this one
uh 512 base EMA 这样 将是一个 V2
uh 512 base EMA so that would be a V2
模型，我将打开它，它是一个 CK
model that I would open up which is a CK
ckpt 形式，然后显然当你
ckpt form and then obviously when you
加载你自己的自定义模型时，你
load your own custom model you're gonna
需要指定它是什么，就像这个
need to specify what it is like this one
是 V2 模型，所以我不必
is a V2 model so I wouldn't have to make
确保我单击 V2 并且它不是 v
sure that I click V2 and it's not a v
参数化 mod，因为它不是
parameterization mod because it's not
768 x 768 版本，因此如果您使用其中一个快速选择，则
this the 768 by 768 version so you have
必须指定实际建模是什么，
to specify what is the actual modeling
if you use one of the Quick Picks for
例如如果我禁用它并且
example if I just if I disable that and
我 再次单击其中一个“快速选择”
I click on one of the Quick Picks again
以获得这个，嗯，我想是
for this one uh well I guess a different
另一个，所以它不是这个，所以现在
one so it's so it's not this one so now
你可以看到它实际上会指定
you can see it will actually specify the
正确的选项，所以如果我进入 2-1 模型，
right option so if I go into a 2-1 model
那么它就会 说它是一个
then it's going to say it's a v
带有 V2 的 v 参数化模型，它
parameterization model with V2 it's all
都包含在那些快速选择中，但是如果
all bakes into those Quick Picks but if
您手动选择 CP ckpt 或
you manually select the CP ckpt or a
保存的答案文件，那么您将必须
saved answer file then you're gonna have
指定这个模型是关于什么的，所以
to specify what this model is about so
为了快速入门，让我们选择一个
for this quick start let's pick one of
这些默认的快速选择，所以我将
these default Quick Picks so I'm going
使用呃稳定扩散 2.1
to go with the uh stable diffusion 2.1
基础，这是一个 512 x 512
base which is a 512 by 512
训练模型，
trained model
接下来你
and the next thing you're going to want
要做的是你会
to do is you're gonna you're gonna want
想要 在实用程序下，这就是
to go under utilities and this is where
我们要为
we're going to structure the actual
cool yes 构建实际文件夹要求的地方，
folder requirements for cool yes as
因为 Koya SS 有一些相当严格
because Koya SS has some fairly strict
和晦涩的结构需要训练
and obscure structure required to train
，今年它会吐它会为
and this year it's gonna spit it's gonna
你准备一切所以你做你
prepare everything for you so you do you
不必理解和担心如何
don't have to understand and worry about
实际命名文件夹结构文件夹等等所以
how to actually name the folders
structure the folders and whatnot so
第一个提示首先是
first prompt first is for the instance
您要使用的实例名称呃通常
name that you're gonna use uh usually
它是
it's a keyword that does not exist
锦鲤 ISS 空间中不存在的关键字抱歉 在
within the koi ISS space Sorry on in the
稳定的扩散空间中，所以你会选择
stable diffusion space so you would pick
像 ASD 这样的东西，在这种情况下，这是
something like ASD in this case which is
一个在模型和课堂上自然已知的标记，
a token that is naturally known within
假设我们
the model and in the class let's say we
想像一个人一样训练，我们将
want to train like a person we're going
使用一个课堂人，
to use a class person
因为 假设
because let's say that that token that
我们要关联的那个标记是一个
we're going to associate with is a
人的训练图像，但我不是来这里
person training image but I'm not here
给你做这个关于
to give you like this speech about how
梦想靴如何工作的演讲，主要是关于
dream boot works and mostly about like
如何使用 Goya SS 进行梦想靴
how to use Goya SS for dream boot
训练呃训练 一个图像那么
training uh training an image so what
你的训练图像在哪里所以
where where are your training image so
在这种情况下训练图像在我的
training image in this case are in my
快速启动文件夹中并且它们在
quick start folder and they are in the
人中呃抱歉在我的子集
person uh sorry in the subset
文件夹中所以我有
folder that I have so I've got a subset
八个图像的子集用于训练 所以我
of eight image for a training so I'm
要使用子集文件夹，
going to use the subset folder
在这里我要指定
and here I'm going to specify how many
我想要这些图像的重复次数我
repeats of those image do I want so do I
想要 40 次重复我想要训练
want 40 repeats do I want to train for
160 次重复例如在这种情况下让我们
160 repeats for example in this case
说 160 次重复 因为
let's say 160 repeats because there is
只有八张图像，而 160 对于使用 koi ISS 呃正则化图像
only eight image and 160 is sort of a
在八张图像上进行训练是一个很好的数字，
good number for training on eight image
using koi ISS uh regularization image do
我想在大多数时候使用正则化图像吗，
I want to use regularization image most
of the time it is a good idea to use
当你尝试远程时使用它们是个好主意所以 我
those when you try to remote so I'm
要去选择正则化
gonna go and pick the regularization
图像文件夹，这将成为我的
image folder which is going to be my
person ddim
因为它是一个 person 类所以我要
because it's a person class so I'm going
训练一个 person 正则化图像
to train a person regularization image
我只想重复
and I only want to repeat the
正则化一次
regularization once
然后你指定你的训练呃
then you specify your training uh
目的地培训目录，这是
destination training directory which is
我想创建我的 Koya SS
where do I want to create my Koya SS
结构化文件夹的地方，所以在这里我要
structured uh folders so here I'm going
继续并再次单击它我要去
to go ahead and click on this again I'm
并在我的快速启动下选择一些东西
going to go and pick something under my
我要打电话
quick start I'm going to call that for
例如，新文件夹，我将其命名为
example new folder I'm going to call it
um
kuya
training，将其
training
call it Korea training
命名为 Korea training，我将选择它作为
and I'm gonna do a good select that as
我的目标文件夹，这样现在我们可以
my destination folder so now we can
单击准备训练数据，
click on prepare training data
它实际上应该启动并且
it should actually fire up and it's
正在运行 告诉你它复制了这些
going to tell you that it copied these
东西 uh 复制了子集到这个
things uh copied the subset to this
文件夹，它复制了 person ddim 到
folder and it copied the person ddim to
这个文件夹，正确的名字是
this folder with the proper name being
你的令牌和类名所以它
your token and the class name so it's
完成了创建所有必需的文件夹
done creating all of the required folder
结构所以我们很好
structure so that we are good to
继续所以接下来要做的
continue so the next thing you want to
是点击复制信息到
do is you want to click on copy info to
目录堆栈因为如果我们
directory stack because if we go to the
现在转到目录样式你可以看到
directory style right now you can see
它是空的它需要像
it's empty it needs to be filled like
图像文件夹正则化
what is the image folder regularization
文件夹输出一样填充 您可以
folder output directory you could
手动进入目录并选择它们，但是
manually go and pick those up but
因为我们使用了这个重启文件夹
because we've used this reboot folder
准备实用程序，我们可以复制我们
preparation utility we can just copy the
info that was actually
picked up by the configured we've typed
在此处输入的配置实际选择的信息，现在它将填充
here and now it's going to fill the
图像文件夹名称 正则化
image folder name the regularization
文件夹命名输出目录，
folder name the output directory where
我们将实际吐出
we're going to actually spit out the
结果模型和登录目录，
resulting model and the login directory
我想
where we're going to log uh I guess the
训练数据
training data
接下来你要做的是
next thing you're going to want to do is
你要去 想要进入
you're going to want to go under the
训练参数，这是
training parameters and this is where
你要指定你梦想的引导
you're going to specify your dream boot
参数的地方，比如添加大小，就像我的情况一样，
parameters like add size like in my case
我有一个相当强大的卡，它是
I have a fairly powerful card it's a
3090，所以如果你喜欢，我可以做八个批量大小
3090 so I can do batch sizes of eight if
一张 vram 较少的卡，那么
you have like a card with less vram then
您可能希望默认情况下将其保持为
you will probably want to keep that to
一个，即
one
epochs 的数量，因此
by default the the number of epochs so
how many iterations of the of the number
of
我们指定的重复次数的迭代次数
repeats that we that we have specified
是我们想要做的，我只想做一个
do we want to do I only want to do one
嗯，这些都是
um how like those are all the typical
您已经知道的所有典型参数，对吧，
parameter that you already know right
我不是很好，我不是要真正
I'm not good I'm not there to really
教您如何进行排水引导，而是教您更多
teach you how to do drain boot but more
如何使用此 GUI 快速开始工作，
how to use this GUI to quickly get going
以便您可以进行配置 就像
so you can go and configure like the
学习数组
different like the learning array
调度程序一样不同，你可以配置
scheduler you can configure like the
你想要的精确度呃什么样的
Precision that you want uh what kind of
模型保存精度
save Precision for the model the the
你想要的输出模型和谐呃
output model that you want Harmony uh
CPU线程每个进程你
CPU threads the per process do you
实际想要实际使用这是
actually want to actually use this is
计算出来的 通过基于您的 CPU
calculated by the GUI based on your CPU
报告信息的 GUI 所以在我的例子中它是
reported information so in my case it's
12 你想用于交易的 C 在哪里
12 where is the C that you want to use
什么是最大
for the trading what is the max
分辨率 这是一个重要的你
resolution this is an important one you
需要指定图像的最大分辨率
need to specify the max resolution of
所以在我的 如果我使用
your image so in my case I'm trading on
512 x 512 图像进行交易，所以我将设置
512 by 512 image so I'm going to set the
最大分辨率，
max resolution to that
如果您使用标题文件而
if you were to use caption files instead
不是使用实际实例名称和
of using the actual instance name and
实际类名称，您可以使用
the actual class name you can use an
扩展文件来提供
extension file to provide the
信息，因此它可能是 txt 文件或
information so it could be a txt file or
DOT 标题文件，因此在这种情况下，我们
a DOT caption file so in this case we're
不会使用我们将
not going to use that we're going to
坚持文件夹命名约定
stick with the folder naming convention
来导出这些虚假信息，因此
for the deriving those disinformation so
我们不会使用 标题文件，
we're not going to use a caption file
然后如果您想
and then if you wanted to stop the text
在训练期间部分停止文本编码，
encoding part way during the training
您可以按百分比指定
you could specify percentage-wise how
like how how many percent of the trading
您想要使用多少百分比的交易，因为
do you want to use that for
这里有一大堆选项，
there's a whole bunch of options here
如果 如果你想
that you can if you don't want token
padding for the training you can specify
使用安全张量作为
it if you want to use safe tensors as
你的模型呃格式而不是bin
your model uh format instead of the bin
当你使用扩散器模型时它会将
when you use diffusers model it will
它们保存为点安全张量你
save them as dot safe tensors uh do you
想要做渐变 checkpointing or not
want to do gradient checkpointing or not
uh do you want to enable buckets I
uh do you want to enable buckets I I
recommend that you keep this or
recommend that you leave this one or
this one on because this is going to
resize your image if you don't enable
buckets if your image are not all of the
same size such as 512 x 512 或
same size like 512 by 512 or anything
类似的东西那么你会
like that then you're gonna get an error
在训练过程中通过启用
during the training by enabling
分桶得到一个错误它将确保
bucketing it will ensure that all of
你的所有图像都适合这个最大
your image fit within this maximum
分辨率空间
resolution space
现金潜在使用原子使用
cash latent using the atoms use
资源管理器这些都是
explorers those are all typical training
你使用的典型训练配置和这个 是
config that you use and this is where
您现在准备做的另一件事，
you are now ready to go one more thing
这很重要，特别是因为我们正在
that's important especially since we are
使用，因为您可以看到基于扩散器的
using as you can see a diffuser based
模型，因为它将
model because it's going to be
从稳定性 AI 下载，如果您愿意，我们需要将
downloaded from stability AI we need to
其保存为不同的
potentially save this as a different
模型 得到一个
model right if you want to get like a
ckpt 文件或一个安全的张量文件，这是
ckpt file or a safe tensors file this is
你要选择我
where you're going to select what is my
想要的最终输出模型的地方，就像我
final output model uh that I want like I
希望你将你要交易的那个扩散器
want you to convert that uh diffuser
模型转换成
model that you're going to trade on into
一个 ckpt 文件，这将
a ckpt file and this is going to create
在最后创建一个 last.c kptpt 文件，
a last.c kptpt file at the end and
因为这里我们使用的是 V2 模型，
because here we are using a V2 model
它还将创建一个最后的
it's also going to create a last that
yaml 文件，GUI 将使用它，例如
yaml file that will be used by GUI like
Auto one one one 来知道什么
Auto one one one one to know what
加载它们时要使用的参数
parameters to use when loading them up
所以在这种情况下让我们假装我们
so in this case Let's Pretend We're
要使用 ckpt 版本或者
going to want to use the ckpt version or
让我们使用安全张量因为这
let's go with safe tensor because this
是新标准它更安全所以它
is the new standard it's safer so it's
被留下而不是创建一个 ckpd 让我们
left instead of creating a ckpd let's
创建一个安全 张量
create a safe tensors
文件格式
file format
然后是的所以我们开始所以我只是
and then yeah so here we go so I'm just
回到这里的源模型或者
gonna go back into Source model here or
它并不重要因为经过
it doesn't really matter because the
训练的模型按钮对于 UI
trained model button is global to the UI
是全局的它可能会在
it's something that might change in the
未来改变但现在 我可以点击
future but for now I could click on
商标，然后你可以
trademark and then you can look at the
返回这里查看输出，你可以
outputs by going back here and you can
在这里看到 UI
see here the actual command that the UI
用于启动培训的实际命令呃
is using to launch the trainings uh
训练下划线 DB 下划线固定点
train underscore DB underscore fixed dot
Pi 所以你可以用它来复制这个 并
Pi so you can use that to copy this and
按摩它，就像你想
massage it as well as if you want to use
在事后使用 CLI 一样，这样你就可以
the CLI after the fact right so you can
从字面上接受该命令并
literally take that command and rerun it
使用此加速启动通过 CLI 重新运行它，
through the CLI using this accelerate
它将开始
launch and it's going to start the
交易会话，就像它在这里所做的那样，
trading session just like it does here
所以我' 我会让训练继续进行，所以
so I'll let the training continue so
它现在正在做的事情我猜它正在用
what it's doing right now I guess it's
caching all of the latents with the
桶缓存所有的潜伏，所以你可以看到它被剪切了，它是在
buckets so as you can see it's cut it's
计算所有图像，并
kind of calculating all of the image and
基于
based on the number of regularization
我的正则化图像的数量 输入现在
image that I have in my input now it's
有点随机化并为
kind of going to go and randomize and
create a matching
每个图像创建一个匹配呃然后每个正则化
per image uh then uh per regularization
图像以随机方式匹配这样
image match in a random manner such that
训练实际上是完全
the training is actually totally
随机的
randomized
嘿
hey
现在缓存所有这些潜在的
is now caching all of those latents
好所以现在它完成了缓存和 正如您所
okay so now it's done caching and as you
看到的，如果我们向上滚动它实际上
can see if we scroll back up it actually
创建了
created
2560 512 乘以 512 潜伏
2560 512 by 512 latents uh for the
训练，
training
那么它将开始
then it's gonna go and start the
训练课程，所以
training session so those five those uh
如果您愿意，这五个 2560 步现在将被压缩
steps if you wish will now be compressed
320，因为在我的情况下，我 我正在使用 8
320 because in my case I'm using eight
um
8 平行三治疗，所以我在
eight parallel three healing so I'm kind
of using this option here under the
训练参数下使用这个选项，使批量
training parameters to have like batch
大小为 8，这就是为什么这个数字
sizes of eight so that's why this number
现在在这里看起来更低，
now is going to look lower in here
因为它实际上是在除以这个
because it's actually dividing this
总数 呃训练步骤
total number of uh training steps by
8 给出 320 现在它
eight which gives 320 and now it's kind
有点缓慢进步并且让你
of slowly progressing and that gives you
了解我在 3090 上获得的速度
an idea of the speed that I get on the
它实际上有点做
3090 it's actually sort of doing
1.2 一点我想它可能会
1.2 one point I guess it's probably
稳定下来到
going to stabilize down to something
类似的东西 1.15 所以它较低，因为我
like 1.15 so that's lower because I'm
同时记录了这个，
kind of recording this at the same time
但训练即将开始，
but the training is going to get going
所以我要暂停这个，然后我将
so I'm going to pause this and then I'm
在训练完成后恢复，
going to resume when the training is
done
阿喀琉斯几乎到了 结束
Achilles were almost to the end
所以大约需要 4 分 35
so it took about 4 minutes and 35
秒来
seconds to
完成
complete
整个处理
the full processing
，
and
现在它保存了模型，现在它正在将
now it saved the model and now it's
模型转换为安全的舞者，所以
converting the model to a safe dancer so
现在你可以看到它把它保存为一个
now as you can see it saved it as a
保存答案的玻璃杯
glass that saved answers
，
and
最后转换保存 保险
finally converting saving the insurance
模型，所以我们都完成了，所以现在我们
model so we're all done so now we have
the model saved
以半精度保存了模型，它实际上也
in half precision and it's actually also
有最后一个
has the required last the camel file for
auto 实际使用它所需的骆驼文件现在让我们
auto to actually use it now let's give
试一试，看看它是否有效，
that a try let's see if it worked
因为那是 整点是对的，我们
because that's the whole point right we
想确保这个模型能正常
want to make sure that this model is
工作，所以我要
going to work so I'm going to go and
启动自动，一张一张
fire up Auto one one one
到这里到
here into here
网络，
to web
所以让我们真正地一张一张地加载照片
so let's actually load photo one one one
，当它这样做的时候我' 我要去
one and while it does that I'm going to
确保模型在
go and make sure the model is in the
正确的地方所以让我们去打开
right place so let's go and open up
山的位置所以这里的模型
the mountain location so here model
应该在
should have been put under a quick start
Koya 训练下快速启动因为
under the Koya training because that's
我们把模型放在那里现在可以在
where we put the model is now found
这里找到 在最后一次和最后一次保存
under here under last and last save
张量下 所以这是模型
tensor so this is the model
是的 更多文件 它在这里如果
yeah more file it goes like this here if
你想使用扩散器版本
you wanted to use the diffuser version
这也是模型的扩散器版本
this is the diffuser version of the
因为我们使用
model as well because we use the
它创建的扩散源
diffuserous source it got created a
最初输出或 作为扩散器，
outputted originally or as a diffuser
然后转换为最后保存的
and then converted to a last.saved
答案并持续了是的所以我们要去
answer and lasted yeah so we're gonna go
复制这两个东西在这里我要把
and copy those two things here I'm gonna
它们转储到我的模型
dump them into my model
文件夹所以模型我要转储它们
folders so models I'm going to dump them
让我们创建一个新的 文件夹在这里 新
let's create a new folder here new
文件夹 我们将称之为
folder that we're going to call it
测试
testing
我要去这里 把那两个模型放在
I'm gonna go here put those two models
那里 让
there
我们去并在 Auto one 中打开它
and let's go and open that up in Auto
one one
我们去这里 让我们开火 让我们
let's go up here let's fire up that
刷新 这样我们就有了 大多数
let's refresh so that we have the most
可用的模型然后让我们来看看
models available and then let's go look
at
测试所以测试最后一个让我们说
testing so testing the last let's say
小张量因为你可以看到它
tensor small as you can see it's picked
在那里被拾取我们要加载它
up there we're gonna load it
我不记得我们
and I don't remember exactly what we
使用的是什么因为
used as the
它是 ESD 人所以让我们 去使用
it was ESD person so let's go and use
这两个标记，看看我们是否可以
those two tokens to see if we can
从那里生成一些东西，
generate something out of there
我们将使用 ESD
we're gonna use ESD
，我们将保留
and we're going to leave the defaults
所有东西的默认值，我们将让它像
for everything we're gonna make it like
一批力一样，我们有我的样本，
batch of force we have my sample and
让我们生成 那里有一些东西
let's generate something out of there
我们走了所以我们有四个
there we go so we have the four
不同的
different outputs
模型输出我可以向你展示
for the model I can show you the
原始输入看起来
original inputs which appear to match
与预期的
quite well with what was expected to be
训练非常匹配所以这些是实际输出让
trained so those are the actual outputs
我们看看实际输入 所以
and let's look at the actual inputs so
这里在每个子集下快速启动，
here under a quick starts under per
我们可以看看
under subset and we can look at the
实际的，
actual
我们将要查看大图标，
we're going to view large icons
嗯，
um
所以我们喜欢这些典型的图像，所以
so we have like these typicals image so
这就是输入的样子
this is what the input is like
，你可以清楚地看到
and you can clearly see that the
结果图像
resulting image are kind of matching the
style
如果我们返回此处，则有点与输入中的样式相匹配，
of what was in the input if we go back
因此您可以看到，如果我们返回
here so you can see that if we go back
to
收音机用户界面，
the radio UI
您可以看到
you can see that
我们的结果非常相似，
we have quite similarly looking results
因此可以得出
so
如何实际使用
that concludes how you can actually use
Koya SS 的结论 用于快速准备您的
Koya SS GUI to quickly prepare your
文件夹结构的 GUI 配置您的训练
folder structure configure your training
参数 选择
parameters select your actual model that
您想要训练的实际模型，然后简单地
you want to train into and then simply
训练您的模型直到
train your model up to the point where
您可以将生成的文件
you can take the resulting files put
放入您的自动 1111 模型文件夹
them into your auto 1111 models folder
或其他一些呃 您可能正在使用的解决方案并将
or some other uh solution that you might
它们用作
be using and use them as a
生成输出的模型
models for generating outputs
希望这很有用并祝大家
hope that was useful and have a great
[音乐]
[Music]
日愉快
day guys
再见
and girls bye